#### Contact

Skopje 1000 Macedonia 070-310-661 (Mobile) jordan.jancevski@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jordanjanchevski-77199b56 (LinkedIn) bit.ly/3iB1zGw (Portfolio)

# Top Skills

Figma (Software)

Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator

# Languages

German (Limited Working) English

#### Certifications

Google UX Design Specialization Figma UI UX Design Essentials

#### Honors-Awards

Honor for representing "Faculty of Economics" internationally

Second Place for Best Business Plan at "Summer Jam 2014", Zadar, Croatia

# Jordan Janchevski

**UX/UI** Designer

Skopje, Skopski, North Macedonia

# Summary

Portfolio Link: https://bit.ly/3iB1zGw

I'm a UX/UI designer with two years of experience in creating userfriendly and visually appealing digital products. I use Figma, and Adobe XD to design wireframes, prototypes, and UIs that meet user needs and business goals.

Additionally, I work with Illustrator and Photoshop to create visuals and enhance the look of what I'm working on.

I also have some knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to collaborate with developers and ensure smooth implementation. I'm passionate about solving problems with empathy and creativity, and I'm always eager to learn new skills and tools.

# Experience

Best Pay Per Click Marketing
UX/UI Designer
December 2022 - Present (4 months)
Chicago, Illinois, United States

Developing responsive layout design for web and mobile, UI/UX design for various applications, building wireframes and prototypes while focusing on landing pages with high conversion rates. I use Figma as primary design tool, and I build the pages using Unbounce. I also include HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery codes while developing the applications.

#### **KidzToPros**

Marketing Consultant | Visual Designer March 2022 - September 2022 (7 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

I actively worked on and oversaw the adoption of Monday.com as a CRM and operational system while working for this start-up; I was working on

building the workflow and established the reporting structure for the marketing department.

I was collaborating directly with the marketing team and designers to ensure that every flyer was created, printed, and distributed accordingly throughout the schools.

Since we were automating Adobe Illustrator, I made sure the entire process went smoothly.

I kept in regular contact with the printer shops and thoroughly monitored the shipping procedure to ensure there were no errors.

### SnapStack

Resource Management Consultant | Visual Designer February 2020 - April 2022 (2 years 3 months)

Prague, The Capital, Czech Republic

As a resource management consultant, it was my responsibility to guarantee that all of our projects had adequate staffing. As a result, I worked to recruit and retain the greatest tech experts possible.

As a member of the design team, I assisted with campaign setup, designing visuals for social media, designing catalogues and did copywriting.

In addition, I was responsible for running reports, managing the CRM, and handling timesheets and administration.

MY:TIME Watches & Jewelry

2 years

Warehouse Manager January 2019 - February 2020 (1 year 2 months) Skopje

Sales Assistant March 2018 - December 2018 (10 months) Skopje

HERA - Health Education and Research Association Volunteer December 2015 - January 2019 (3 years 2 months) Skopje, Macedonia Member of a pool of trainers on Comprehensive Sexual Education | Certified peer-educator in the fields of CSE

Hosting and developing a radio program

Administrating a fan page for youth, health and rights

Communication with schools, organizations and partners for implementing joint activities

#### **ENH Live**

Copywriter

January 2017 - November 2017 (11 months)

Skopje

### Stopanska banka AD - Skopje

4 years 7 months

Archivist

July 2012 - January 2017 (4 years 7 months)

Archiving credit files at Credit Administration Department

#### Intern

July 2013 - August 2013 (2 months)

Skopje, Macedonia

#### **AIESEC**

3 years

Team member | Outgoing exchanges 2012 - December 2015 (3 years)

Skopje

Team member | Outgoing exchanges

Part of the "Interview and raising" team

Oranization Committee President

August 2013 - May 2014 (10 months)

Project manager of "Career Direction '14"

OC member

February 2013 - April 2013 (3 months)

OC team member of the "Career direction" project.

# Education

### Brainster

Full-stack Web Developer, Web Development · (2017 - 2018)

University of Cyril and Methodius Skopje Faculty of Economics - Management · (2012 - 2016)

SEPUGS "Vasil Antevski - Dren" Law technician, Law technician · (2008 - 2012)